{
    "id": "c690d843f5b14c92ba3775d22558be28",
    "title": "Passive Voice Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The winners …………………………. by all.",
            "description": "In the simple past tense, the passive form is made with was/were + past participle form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "have congratulated",
                "were congratulating",
                "were congratulated"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He ……………………………. after he complained of chest pain.",
            "description": "In the simple past tense, the passive form is made with was/were + past participle form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "has hospitalized",
                "was hospitalized",
                "had hospitalized"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "It ……………………… that the prices of oil will increase after the election.",
            "description": "In the simple present tense, the passive form is made with is/am/are + past participle form of the verb. ",
            "answers": [
                "is speculated",
                "is speculating",
                "has speculated"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He ……………………… for possessing firearms.",
            "description": "In the simple past tense, the passive form is made with was/were + past participle form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "arrested",
                "has arrested",
                "was arrested"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "My questions ……………………….",
            "description": "The active form is 'They have answered my questions'. In the present perfect, the passive form is made with has/have + past participle form of the verb. ",
            "answers": [
                "have answered",
                "has been answered",
                "have been answered"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………… to their party.",
            "description": "In the simple past tense, the passive form is made with was/were + past participle form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "didn't invite",
                "was not invited",
                "have not invited"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The parcel ……………………… in the morning.",
            "description": "In the simple past tense, the passive form is made with was/were + past participle form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "sent",
                "has sent",
                "was sent"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The results ……………………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have announced",
                "have been announced",
                "had announced"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Football ………………………… all over the world.",
            "description": "In the simple present tense, the passive form is made with is/am/are + past participle form of the verb. ",
            "answers": [
                "played",
                "is played",
                "have played"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The label …………………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "should not remove",
                "should not removed",
                "should not be removed"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Do not accept this product if the seal …………………….",
            "description": "In the simple present tense, the passive form is made with is/am/are + past participle form of the verb. ",
            "answers": [
                "breaks",
                "has broken",
                "is broken"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He ………………………… by millions of people all over the world.",
            "description": "In the simple present tense, the passive form is made with is/am/are + past participle form of the verb. ",
            "answers": [
                "admired",
                "has admired",
                "is admired"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}